Victor Kean

PHONE NUMBER: 254726737011 | EMAIL: greenlink@mailfence.com

Experienced Full Stack Developer adapt in all stages of advanced software development. Drive performance turning, query plans, indexing and table partitioning. Write reusable unit test documents to ensure quality control and identify bugs. Able to effectively self-manage during independent projects, as well as collaborate in a team setting. Highly motivated, skilled and passionate web developer. Challenging every day, to grow, to learn and to improve and bring the best of my experience and abilities to my complementary roles. Happy working remotely as I am when getting together in the office and am open to and enthusiastic about working with team members across multiple geographic locations.

SKILLS

- PHP, Laravel
- HTML5, SCSS, CSS
- Angular2+
- Vue.js
- React.js
- React Native
- Mobile Application Development
- Security implementation
- Coding
- Technical analysis
- Debug software
- Program logic creation
- Validate code
- Produce clean code
- Update software

Experience

Senior Web Developer (BBN Company) – Japan, Hukuoka

08/2018 to 03/2021

- Developed , tested, deployed, and maintained web application
- Provided effective troubleshooting and remediation for web applications
- Wrote SQL statements and stored procedures
- Worked well within a team setting
- Effectively translated client requirements into application designs.

FreelanceR 10/2016 to Current

Com and peopleperhour.com

- Build React native app from scratch,
- Upgrade React native app to latest version
- Fix bugs on existing source
- Redesign existing React native app.

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Science degree in Software Engineering, Computer Software Engineering February 2010 - August 2014

University of Nairobi

ACCOMPLISHMENT

React Native

- https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.switch_android&hl=en_US&gl=US
 https://apps.apple.com/us/app/neurocycle/id1460119837
- https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.ohs.head_start_resources
- https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.vhx.reveal

Android Studio (JAVA)

https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.innewsmagazines.lite.miniielts

PHP, Laravel

- https://beacon-cloud.biz : BBN Company Business System
- https://www.jigsawtrading.com : Stock Marketing Site
- https://anyrateauto.com/ : Car repair Site
- http://homeworkstudy.net/ : Homework Site
- https://studyace.net/ : Homework Site
- https://www.mealsuite.com/: Food service software
- https://www.innquest.com/roommaster anywhere : hotel room reservation system
- https://balimotors.co.uk : Laravel , Quality car retailer of Stoke
- https://web.truelance.net: job site
- https://mylocahron.com : company management system
- https://lish-eikaiwa.jp : online site for english teachers out of Phillipines
- https://buzzamplify.com : marketing solution delivered on the cloud

Wordpress:

- https://www.domenicagroup.com/ : Real Estate
- https://denura.co.uk : Belt Shop

https://caringforcare.co.uk: HealthCare E-Learning Website

WIX

- https://www.animalresearchconversation.com/ : Animal Research Ambassador
- https://www.thrifty-gentleman.com : e-Shop

ADDITIONAL INFO

• LinkedIn: www.linkedin.com/in/victorkean-654a12251